Guide to the Richard Pollay Acme Advertising Collection, 1850s-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 23: Matchbook Covers, 2000s and undated
  - 100-23-034. Acme Paper. Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Front cover and back covers show logo of Acme Paper and company information. Inside cover reads: Distributors of Champion Mill Brand Papers. Unstruck, no matches; Universal Match (St. Louis) product. In excellent condition.
  - 100-23-035. Lyon's Café. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Front cover shows company information and a sign Cities Service. Back cover reads Ride to Victory on Acme Tires. and drawing of a tire, jeep and a factory with blowing smokestacks. Struck, no matches, stained, small tear at the back.
  - 100-23-036. Acme Mills, Inc. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Silver papered match cover advertises Veribest Short Patent flour, Dove Self-Rising Flour, and Blue Wing Self Rising Flour on its front and back. Unstruck, no matches. Royal Flash Billboard Match by Universal Match Corp product, patent pending.
  - 100-23-037. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Beer match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Colored plastic replica of the Acme Beer match cover, showing drawings of the Acme beer and Acme ale bottles and the words Acme quality wins again! Fine print on the bottom of the item is The Ohio Match Company Wadsworth, Ohio. Looks like a refrigerator match cover magnet.
  - 100-23-038. Acme Inn. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Front cover shows Lady in distress, a colored drawing of woman in her undergarments. Back cover reads: Cocktails Acme Inn, Clearlake Highlands, Lake County, Cal., Ted and Nancy Woods, Bottled goods to take out. Unstruck, with complete set of matches. Matches made by Chicago Match Company, Libertyville, Ill.
  - 100-23-039. Mahan, McCarty and Bessie Inc. Acme Lumber Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Colored match cover with Mahan, McCarty and Bessie, Inc., Big Building and Construction Contractors. Text and logo on front cover. Back cover reads Acme Lumber Company, General Office Hunt Building, Tulsa, Oklahoma. Struck, no matches. Match cover made by Lion Match Company.
  - 100-23-040. Acme Motors. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Front of match cover is a colored photograph of a 1975 Plymouth Gran Fury Brougham Front; back cover shows company information for Acme Motors of Kittanning, Penn. Cover shows company information. Intact with matches. Unstruck. Excellent condition.comes with post-it note: eBay # 7142713166 Acme Motors Kittanning, Penn. matchbook. Match cover made by Universal Match, Detroit.
  - 100-23-041. Acme Fast Freight, Inc. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Unusual-sized match cover. Red cover, opens up to show matches with Acme Fast Freight, Inc. painted on matchsticks. Unstruck, with matches. Front cover reads If you can't cut labor, raw material or production costs, you can look to Acme to cut transportation costs.
  - 100-23-042. Acme Pipe Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Gold match book cover. Matches removed. Acme pipe company--Distributors of Republic Pipe--Pipes Valves Fittings Plumbing Supplies. Match book manufactured by Universal Match Corp, St. Louis, M. O.
  - 100-23-043. Acme Cleaners. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Orange match cover. Matches removed. Acme Cleaners--Your Sanitone Cleaners. Match cover manufactured by Mercury Match, Zanesville, O.
  - 100-23-044. Acme Dairy Products Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Beige match cover. Matches removed. Always Ask for Acme Dairy Products--Try Acme Fiesta Ice Cream.
  - 100-23-045. Michigan Acme Iron Works. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Match cover. Matches removed. Michigan Acme Iron Works--Pioneer Builders of Truck Excavators. Rust stains around staple holes.
  - 100-23-046. Acme Bar and Grill Annapolis. Match cover, 2000s (Box 41)
    White match cover with black lettering. Matches removed. Acme Bar and Grill Annapolis--Think Globally Drink Locally. Manufactured by H and M Wagner and Sons, Glen Burnie, MD.
  - 100-23-047. Acme Cab and Baggage Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Match cover. Matches removed. Acme Cab and Baggage Company--Phone 4171--Sight Seeing Tours of the Palm Beaches--Two-way radio assures you faster service anytime--anyplace--Baggage Pick-up and Delivery Service.
  - 100-23-048. Acme Ind. Life Insurance Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Blue match cover with silver lettering. Acme Ind. Life Insurance--What Is Life Without Protection--Call Acme Today.
  - 100-23-049. Acme Electric Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Match Cover. Matches removed. Acme Electric Co.--We Are Always Happy To Serve You. Pin-up girl on back with text: A Bumper Crop. Manufactured by Match Corp. of America.
  - 100-23-050. Acme Roofing Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Another Good Roof by ACME Roofing Co.--The Sign of Progress. Black lettering on white background. Matches removed. As new condition.
  - 100-23-051. Acme Awning and Shade Company. Match cover, undated (Box 41)
    Match cover. Color image of boy with dog Partners. Acme Awning and Shade Company. Some fading. Matches removed.
- Series 24: Telephone Directories, 1976 and undated
  - 100-24-001. Unknown. Telephone Advertising. Binder 1, 1976 (No image available) (Box 41)
    Photocopied pages from Telephone books. Provenance is unknown. Date is taken from the original binder.
  - 100-24-002. Unknown. Telephone Advertising. Binder 2, undated (No image available) (Box 41)
  - 100-24-003. Unknown. Yellow Pages, undated (Box 11)
    Collage of assorted Acme advertising that has been taken from Yellow Pages of unknown provenance. Ads have been glued to black backing. Good condition.
  - 100-24-004. Unknown. Yellow Pages, undated (Box 11)
    Collage of assorted Acme advertising that has been taken from Yellow Pages of unknown provenance. Ads have been glued to white backing. Good condition.
- Series 25: Business cards, undated
  - 100-25-001. Binder of Business cards, undated (No image available) (Box 41)
    Binder contains 138 business cards. Country of origin and quality varies.
- Series 26: Trade Cards, 1882-1891 and undated
  - 100-26-001. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap! Top of the Heap! Sure to please! Will do honest work! No more yellow clothes! Image of red and yellow roses against snow scene. Minor crease. Good condition.
  - 100-26-002. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Image of girl washing. Catalog reverse: Lusk and Marsh Dealers in Groceries and Provisions. Good condition.
  - 100-26-003. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Image of girl blowing bubbles. Good condition.
  - 100-26-004. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Soap Cut Full Pounds. The Best Bar Soap Made. Gold back ground, image of baby in white clothes. Good condition.
  - 100-26-005. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Soap Cut Full Pounds. The Best Bar Soap Made. Gold back ground, image of young boy in white/striped clothes. Pencil scribbled on back of card. Good condition.
  - 100-26-006. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Cut Full Pounds. Best Bar Soap Made. Image of girl and apple tree. Good condition. Reverse: W. Kage Dealers in Choice Family Groceries.
  - 100-26-007. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Cut Full Pounds. Best Bar Soap Made. Image of girl and potted plant. Good condition. Reverse: E. L. and G. D. Kenyon Dealers in Staple and fancy Groceries.
  - 100-26-008. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Cut Full Pounds. Best Bar Soap Made. Image of girl smelling roses. Good condition. Reverse: W. Kage Dealers in Choice Family Groceries.
  - 100-26-009. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Image of 3 girls in geisha (?) costumes. Good condition. Reverse: W. E. Woodbury Wholesale and retail Groceries.
  - 100-26-010. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1880s (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Image of Man in Samurai (?) costume. Good condition. Reverse: Bought at Wooster and Boothe, Gash (sic) dealers in Staple and Fancy Groceries, Provisions.
  - 100-26-011. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Image of Man in oriental (?) costume. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-012. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with large hat leaning on fence. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-013. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with hand on paper. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-014. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with hands clasped holding reticule. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-015. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with hands clasped holding rose basket. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-016. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with hands clasped roller skating past boy. Good condition. Reverse: C. A. Leland and Son. Dealers in General Merchandise.
  - 100-26-017. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    If You Want The Best Bar Soap For Laundry Use Acme. Cut Full Pounds. Manufactured by Lautz Bros and Company. Buffalo. Boy holding potted plant for girl. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros advertising.
  - 100-26-018. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Boy whittling wood stick. Good condition.
  - 100-26-019. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl on sled. Good condition.
  - 100-26-020. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl with white bird on shoulder dressed in pink holding rose. Good condition. Reverse: J. W. Baker Druggist and Grocer, Little Falls N.Y.
  - 100-26-021. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl holding basket of grapes. Good condition. Reverse: J. W. Baker Druggist and Grocer, Little Falls N.Y.
  - 100-26-022. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl holding basket of flowers. Good condition. Reverse: J. W. Baker Druggist and Grocer, Little Falls N.Y.
  - 100-26-023. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Girl holding basket of apples. Good condition. Reverse: J. W. Baker Druggist and Grocer, Little Falls N.Y.
  - 100-26-024. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Pure and Healthy Soaps'. Best in the Market. Three children playing outside. Good condition.
  - 100-26-025. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Pure and Healthy Soaps'. Best in the Market. Two girls skipping. Good condition.
  - 100-26-026. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Pure and Healthy Soaps. Best in the Market. Two children playing badminton. Good condition.
  - 100-26-027. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Co's Acme Soap. Pure and Healthy Soaps. Best in the Market. Two girls in snow scene. Good condition.
  - 100-26-028. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    For the Laundry. Use Acme Soap and Niagara Starch. Swain Earl and Company Wholesale Agents, Boston. Red and Green image of child in clown costume. Good condition.
  - 100-26-029. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
  - 100-26-030. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    For the Laundry. Use Acme Soap and Niagara Starch. Swain Earl and Company Wholesale Agents, Boston. Red and Green image of child (?) blowing bubbles. Good condition.
  - 100-26-031. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    For the Laundry. Use Acme Soap and Niagara Starch. Swain Earl and Company Wholesale Agents, Boston. Red and Green image of child standing on bubble. Good condition.
  - 100-26-032. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    For the Laundry. Use Acme Soap and Niagara Starch. Swain Earl and Company Wholesale Agents, Boston. Red and Green image of child in costume balancing bubble on the end of his nose. Good condition.
  - 100-26-033. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young girl wearing ruffled cap. Good condition. Reverse: Acme soap advertising. The Height in perfection. Solicitation to send in soap wrappers for products.
  - 100-26-034. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young girl blowing bubbles in cup. Good condition. Reverse: Acme soap advertising. The Height in perfection. Solicitation to send in soap wrappers for products.
  - 100-26-035. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young boy blowing bubbles from pipe. Good condition. Reverse: C. M. Young and Company Grocers Niagara Falls, N.Y.
  - 100-26-036. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap (Cut Full Pounds) best Bar Soap Made. Mfd by Lautz Bros and Company. Child in costume holding peacock feather. Good condition.
  - 100-26-037. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap (Cut Full Pounds) best Bar Soap Made. Mfd by Lautz Bros and Company. Child in toga style dress-up. Good condition.
  - 100-26-038. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap (Cut Full Pounds) best Bar Soap Made. Mfd by Lautz Bros and Company. Child in costume holding butterfly on finger. Good condition.
  - 100-26-039. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap Premium Cat, undated (Box 41)
    Premiums given for Lautz Bros and Company Big Master Acme, Circus, Gloss and Marseilles White Soap Wrappers. Folded and creased. Fragile condition.
  - 100-26-040. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap Wrapper, undated (Box 41)
    Monocled man holding bar of Acme Soap. The Best Bar Soap Made. Good condition.
  - 100-26-041. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Monocled man holding bar of Acme Soap.The Best Bar Soap Made. Good condition. Reverse: Henry L. Parsons Wholesale Grocer and Commission Merchant. Providence RI.
  - 100-26-042. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Monocled man holding bar of Acme Soap. The Best Bar Soap Made. Good condition. Reverse: The place to get goods at reasonable prices is A. G. Case at his store in Bristol centre.
  - 100-26-043. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Company's PURE and HEALTHY SOAPS. Best on the market. Seaside scene. Girl carrying Acme Soap. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros and Company Advertising.
  - 100-26-044. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Lautz Bros and Company's PURE and HEALTHY SOAPS. Best on the market. Seaside scene. Boy dragging large black boot. Good condition. Reverse: Lautz Bros and Company Advertising.
  - 100-26-045. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Marseilles White, Gloss, Master, White Spray Soaps--Snow Boy... Small marks and stains. Good condition. Reverse: Leo L. Fox dealer in Choice Family Groceries. Springville N.Y.
  - 100-26-046. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Marseilles White, Gloss, Master, White Spray Soaps. --Hailing the Ferryman... Badly creased and stained. Fragile condition. Reverse: Burgard Bros. Dealers in Groceries and Provisions. Buffalo, N.Y..
  - 100-26-047. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Children in costume dancing around hatching yellow chick. Good condition.
  - 100-26-048. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Children in costume looking at the hatching yellow chick. Good condition. Reverse: R. H. Please Dealers in Groceries, Boots and Shoes. Florence, Mass.
  - 100-26-049. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Children in costume looking like a prince and princess in egg shell. Good condition. Reverse: R. H. Please Dealers in Groceries, Boots and Shoes. Florence, Mass.
  - 100-26-050. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1882 (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Boy holding yellow flowers. Good condition. Reverse: J. A. Kavanagh Dealer in Fine Groceries, Auburn N.Y.
  - 100-26-051. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1882 (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Girl in garden holding large leaf over her head. Good condition. Reverse: Crawford Bros, General Merchandise, Grain and Hay. Cameron Mills N.Y.
  - 100-26-052. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1882 (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Girl in garden looking at bird on branch, doll at her feet. Good condition. Reverse: J. A. Kavanagh Dealer in Fine Groceries, Auburn N.Y.
  - 100-26-053. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap.--Be careful Willie, don't fall! Girl holding jacket of small boy who is holding bar of Acme Soap and bending over well. Good condition. Reverse: Has paper from scrap book attached.
  - 100-26-054. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap--Oh dear, Willie will be drowned! Girl watching as small boy falls in well. Good condition. Reverse: H. V. Hughes Dealer in Confections, Fancy Groceries, Saginaw, Mich.
  - 100-26-055. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap--Why the foam is bringing him up! Girl watching as soap foam brings boy safely up from well. Good condition. Reverse: Cutler, Plimpton and Company Dry and Fancy Goods, Groceries, Florence, Mass.
  - 100-26-056. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. --Saved by Acme Soap! Girl helps boy climb out from soap foam. Good condition. Reverse: Cutler, Plimpton and Company Dry and Fancy Goods, Groceries, Florence, Mass.
  - 100-26-057. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1887? (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Flowers on left hand side, text and yellow soap bar lower left corner. Good condition. Reverse: I. N. Scott and Son, Dealers in Groceries Crockery and Glassware, Glens Falls, N.Y.
  - 100-26-058. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1887? (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Flowers on left hand side, text and yellow soap bar lower left corner. Good condition. Reverse: A. W. Burns Commission Merchant, Utica N.Y.
  - 100-26-059. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1887? (Box 41)
  - 100-26-060. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card--photograph, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Best Bar Soap Made. Cut Full Pounds. Flowers on left hand side, text and yellow soap bar lower left corner. Color photograph of original card. Good condition. Reverse: stamped ACME Photo (604) 224-7322.
  - 100-26-061. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    If You Want The Best Bar Soap For Laundry Use ACME. Cut Full Pounds. Manufactured by Lautz Bros and Company Buffalo. Child wrapped in shawl holding flowers. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising.
  - 100-26-062. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    If You Want The Best Bar Soap For Laundry Use ACME. Cut Full Pounds. Manufactured by Lautz Bros and Company Buffalo. Two young children embracing. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising.
  - 100-26-063. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1886 (Box 41)
    If You Want The Best Bar Soap For Laundry Use ACME. Cut Full Pounds. Manufactured by Lautz Bros and Company Buffalo. Young woman in eastern style costume. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising.
  - 100-26-064. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Cut Full Pounds. Best Bar Soap Made. Mfd by Lautz Bros and Company Buffalo. Two girls, one wearing white head gear, one wearing black head gear, knitting. Good condition. Reverse: blank, number 10 in pencil.
  - 100-26-065. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Girl leaning over large book. Good condition. Reverse: J. and F Williams, Grocers, Niagara Falls, N.Y.
  - 100-26-066. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Girl covering boys eyes. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising, Andy Welch, Dealer in Staple, Fancy, Dry Goods. Logansport, Ind.
  - 100-26-067. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1884 (Box 41)
    Use Acme. Cut Full Pounds. Best Bar Soap Made. Two girls mixing something in small containers Good condition. Reverse: Newark, N. Y, 1884, M-...Bo't of A. Williams, Dealer in Groceries and Provisions.
  - 100-26-068. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Young child in high chair writing with quill. Gold background. Yellowing. Good condition. Reverse: Emily Hall, from your school mate Ada B.
  - 100-26-069. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, 1889 (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Seated girl in white bonnet with blue ribbon. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising.
  - 100-26-070. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young girl in dark striped outfit, holding book. Good condition. Reverse: W. Gallup and Son, Dealers in Groceries...Victor, N.Y.
  - 100-26-071. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young boys floating boats in barrel of water. Good condition. Reverse: W. Gallup and Son, Dealers in Groceries--Victor, N.Y.
  - 100-26-072. Lautz Bros. and Company. Acme Soap trade card, undated (Box 41)
    Use Acme Soap. Leader in Quality. Young girl in flower adorned wagon, accompanied by young boy. Some damage to front of picture. Good condition. Reverse: Acme Soap advertising; Andy Welch, Dealer in Staple, Fancy, Dry Goods. Logansport, Ind.